Hello friends, you are very welcome.
Friends, today in this video we will talk about the
roles and responsibilities of an agency manager.
We will try to understand
what an agency manager
is or what work an agency manager does in the agency.
So without any
delay, let us try to understand what the
roles and responsibilities of an agency manager are.
Friends, the
job of an agency manager is to
manage the sales of the agency channel. An
agency manager is a person,
or we can say that he is a
professional, whose job is to manage the agents who are the
agency agents,
train them, and achieve the team's sales
targets.
Here we can say agency sales manager. The
job of an agency manager is to supervise every aspect of the agency. The
coordinator should
work with the agency and clients,
recruit agents,
train them, evaluate the performance of agents,
and create an action plan to meet the sales targets.
Follow the agency's staff time management and establish the
agency's regulation
guidelines.  The key to this is to ensure that the
agency staff follows the regulations, policies, and
balances, and
maintains discipline.
Researching industry or market trends is the primary job of an
agency sales manager or agency manager.
If you
want to become an agency manager, you should have at
least a full-time degree in marketing or
management or a B.A.,
and to become an agency manager,
you should have at least some
experience in an agency or a
managerial exam. The
basic requirements for becoming an agency manager are
that
your leadership skills should be very good. You should have good
people skills. You should have good
time management skills. You should have good
networking skills
because the job of an agency manager is to
connect with willing people. In which you should have
leadership skills. You should have good people skills.
You should have good networking skills. I hope friends, you liked this video.
If you liked this video,
please subscribe to my channel whose name
is Vinod Singh Thakur. And please like and
comment on my channel now.  That's all for and
thanks watching